http://www.theindustrysource.com/security-privacy-policies

Cookies and Privacy
This website use cookies to ensure you get the best user experience on our website.
Skip to Content
ORDERS PLACED BEFORE 3PM EST SHIP SAME DAY!
TNG Worldwide
Menu
New ArrivalsEssentialsHairMani/PediSpaBrands
EssentialsDisinfectants & AccessoriesDisinfecting WipesDispensersGlovesHand SanitizerMasks & ShieldsNon-Contact ThermometerSterilizing Tray & PouchesHand SoapMani/PediAccessoriesMani/Pedi KitAcrylicMasks & ScrubsBlock BuffersNail & Gel Polish RemoverBoards & FilesNail AccessoriesCallus & Cuticle RemoversNail BrushCuticle SticksNail PolishDip PowderNail Polish Racks & DisplaysElectric FilingPumice & BlocksFlip FlopsSlippersFoot Baths & LinersSoaks & CleanersFoot Files & RaspsSundriesGel Nail PolishToe SeparatorsImplementsTreatmentsLED Nail LampsSpaBody TreatmentsFlip FlopsFurnitureHair RemovalHospitalityLash & BrowMakeup & SkincareMassageParaffinSpa AccessoriesHairBrush & CombsFoil SheetsFurnitureHair AccessoriesHair ColorHair Salon ApparelHair Shampoo, Condition & TreatmentsHair ToolsComfortsAroma DiffusersBath Creamers & BombsEssential OilsFizzy BombsNespressoSalt LampsShower BlastsWax Melters, Bars & CandlesClearanceComfortsHairMani/PediSpa
Quick Order
Home
Security & Privacy Policies
Security & Privacy Policies
Security
Secure Sockets Layering (SSL) tngworldwide.com uses Secure Socket Layering (SSL) to tokenize your personal credit information, including your credit card number before it travels over the Internet. SSL technology is the industry standard for secure online transactions. Because we use SSL, placing an order online at tngworldwide.com is just as safe as giving your credit card number over the phone.
Our Safe Shopping Guarantee When you shop at tngworldwide.com, you are protected by our Safe Shopping Guarantee: If your credit card information is stolen because you used your credit card to make an online purchase from tngworldwide.com, we'll make sure you don't have to pay any fraudulent charges made to your account. Here's how it works:
If fraudulent charges are made to your credit card, you must notify your credit card company in accordance with its rules and procedures. Under the Fair Credit Billing Act, your credit card company cannot require you to pay more than $50.00 of the fraudulent charges.
If your credit card company requires you to pay any part of this $50.00, then tngworldwide.com will reimburse you up to $50.00. We will do so only if the unauthorized use of your credit card number occurred because you used it to purchase something online through tngworldwide.com and only if you properly notified your credit card company.
Privacy
What information do we collect?
Generally, you may browse the website without providing any personally identifiable information. However, we may ask you to provide personally identifiable information at various times and places on this website. In some cases, if you choose not to provide us with the requested information, you may not be able to access all of this website or participate in all of its features.
We receive and store any personally identifiable information you enter on the website, when you shop with TNG Worldwide—online, or information you give us in any other way, such as by subscribing to our email, or contests. For example, we may collect the following personally identifiable information: your name, address, telephone number, mobile telephone number, driver's license number, birth date, and email address. If you use a credit or debit card or pay by check, we will also include your account number.
When you register with us as an online customer, we may ask for additional information, such as your favorite designers.
If you use one of our services, or participate in one of our surveys, promotions, or sweepstakes, we may ask for additional information, such as your age, interests, or product preferences.
From your purchases and other interactions with us, we obtain information concerning the specific products or services you purchase or use.
When you visit this website, our web server automatically collects anonymous information such as log data and IP addresses. We may use the automatically collected information for a number of purposes, such as improving our site design, product assortments, customer service, and special promotions.
How do we use it?
We collect personally identifiable information about you to provide products, services and membership benefits you request; improve the content of our site; enhance your shopping experience; and for marketing and promotional purposes.
tngworldwide.com uses technology that lets us know what type of browser you are using, the website from which you enter tngworldwide.com and the pages you view as you tour our site. This technology does not identify you personally - it simply helps us compile statistics about our guests and their use of our site. We use these statistics to improve our website design and content.
If you do not wish to receive promotional information as a result of using tngworldwide.com website, please send your request to: unsubscribe@tngworldwide.com.
Cookies, Web Beacons, and How We Use Them:
A "cookie" is a small data file stored by your Web browser on your computer's hard drive. It allows us to recognize your computer (but not specifically who is using it) upon entering our site by associating the identification numbers in the cookie with other customer information you have provided us. That customer information is stored on our secured database. A "web beacon" or "pixel tag" or "clear gif" is typically a one-pixel image, used to pass information from your computer to a website
We use cookies and web beacons to keep track of what you have in your shopping cart and to remember you when you return to the website as well as to identify the pages you click on during your visit to our site and the name of the website you visited immediately before clicking to NeimanMarcus.com. We use this information to improve our site design, product assortments, customer service, and special promotions. You can, of course, disable cookies and web beacons on your computer by indicating this in the preferences or options menus in your browser. However, it is possible that some parts of our website will not operate correctly if you disable cookies.
We may contract with third parties who may use cookies and web beacons and collect information on our behalf or provide services such as credit card processing, shipping, promotional services, or data management. We call them our Customer Care Partners. These third parties are prohibited by our contract with them from sharing that information with anyone other than us or our other Customer Care Partners.
Your Consent By using www.tngworldwide.com website, you consent to our use of your information as described in this Online Privacy Policy.
You have no items to compare.
You have no items in your wish list.
Sign up to be the first to know about new products, promotions, and more!
Newsletter
Sign Up for Our Newsletter:
Copyright © 2020 TNG Worldwide, Inc. All rights reserved.
click here
